<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<anime id="6751" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2009-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">11 Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">イレブンアイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">11 глаз</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">أحد عشر عيناً</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">11 akių</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">11eyes: Tsumi to Batsu to Aganai no Shoujo</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">11eyes -罪與罰與贖的少女-</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">罪与罚与赎的少女</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">11 چشم</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">11eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">11 Eyes</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3408" approval="20" total="45">Shakugan no Shana</anime>
<anime id="5357" approval="19" total="24">Night Wizard The Animation</anime>
<anime id="8229" approval="16" total="24">Itsuka Tenma no Kuro Usagi</anime>
<anime id="6088" approval="5" total="10">Chaos;Head</anime>
<anime id="3348" approval="2" total="16">Fate/Stay Night</anime>
<anime id="5544" approval="2" total="9">Persona: Trinity Soul</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="296782">suddenly other world apearance , sudden gathering of poeple with super powers with no rational reason why, watch it if you just want kill some time,</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="385974">Underrated anime the story is so cool but it would be better if it was longer I recommend this anime for everyone</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="235338">This Anime is good in the beginning but got a bit out in the end. It would be better if they would do a second season to rectify the negative impact.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="391151">I really like this series. If you liked Shakugan No Shana but disliked most of second season, then you`ll definitely love this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="333496">Great plot and character development, stunning animation and good soundtrack. (The ending`s a real shame though. Better to stop at episode 11.)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.mmv.co.jp/special/11eyes/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1067" type="Animation Work">Doga Kobo</name>
<name id="2323" type="Series Composition">Kanemaki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="4138" type="Direction">Shimoda Masami</name>
<name id="7016" type="Character Design">Hara Masaharu</name>
<name id="7016" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hara Masaharu</name>
<name id="23689" type="Original Work">Lass</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the 11eyes — Tsumi to Batsu to Aganai no Shoujo adult PC game by developer http://anidb.net/cr23689 [Lass].
The Red Night — it appears without warning. Real, yet unreal. A dark world which exists in an alternate dimension. The Fragments, boys and girls who have been dragged inside are being attacked by strange black knights. Why them? Just what will happen? Will an answer await them at the end of this nightmare? — from intro
Seven teen classmates are transported to another world magic where they must defeat six black knights in order to return home.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1921">3.01</permanent>
<temporary count="1947">6.06</temporary>
<review count="2">3.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>32901.jpg</picture>
<categories>
<category id="241" parentid="313" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Harem</name>
<description>Three or more characters, generally female, are under the influence of one character, normally male. Their interactions are romantically or sexually loaded. The female characters often draw heavily from stock archetypes. Sexual tones are applied to the lead`s behavior and to the members` depiction. The lead will often be physically abused for his behavior. The harem may be only a support to an existing or predictable relationship, or the lead may end up in relationships with most or all members.</description>
</category>
<category id="56" parentid="318" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Tentacle</name>
<description>Tentacles are elongated flexible organs. In anime those are usually used for rape or groping. Tentacle rape is a concept, where various tentacled creatures (usually fictional monsters) rape or otherwise penetrate women (or, less commonly, men).</description>
</category>
<category id="293" parentid="269" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Dating Sim - Visual Novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</category>
<category id="4" parentid="313" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting. </description>
</category>
<category id="271" parentid="269" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Erotic Game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.&#13;
&#13;
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</category>
<category id="79" parentid="3" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Seinen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word seinen refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "young man", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</category>
<category id="18" parentid="4" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Super Power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
</category>
<category id="173" parentid="4" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>Swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
</category>
<category id="60" parentid="318" hentai="false" weight="500">
<name>Female Student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
</category>
<category id="239" parentid="21" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>High School</name>
<description>The upper-secondary education (not compulsory in Japan) covers the grades ten, eleven, and twelve. The students are typically fifteen to eighteen years old.&#13;
&#13;
Anime centre on High School settings predominately: Plot/story-wise the coming of age is of interest - the students are almost adults (their bodies have matured, see ecchi anime) with more earnest, real-life problems.</description>
</category>
<category id="235" parentid="317" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</category>
<category id="86" parentid="83" hentai="false" weight="100">
<name>Sex</name>
<description>Known as intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting).</description>
</category>
<category id="283" parentid="282" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
</category>
<category id="175" parentid="15" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Magic</name>
<description>In a traditional Fantasy anime with medieval setting, the lack of technology is "compensated" by the introduction of the supernatural, i.e. spell-casting, magic wands, and magic circles. &#13;
&#13;
In another setting long-lost technology may be so advanced that it is mistaken for magic (Arthur C. Clarke: "Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic"). See also related tag: science and magic coexist.</description>
</category>
<category id="198" parentid="313" hentai="false" weight="100">
<name>Romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
</category>
<category id="209" parentid="291" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Parallel Universe</name>
<description>Parallel universe/world or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we`ll use the term "Parallel Universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own universe (meaning a fantasy world can just as well have an alternative reality, doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 universe/reality/world is present in the anime.</description>
</category>
<category id="52" parentid="50" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Large Breasts</name>
<description>Focus on larger than average breasts. Pretty common in anime. Usually involves adolescent girls or fully grown women.</description>
</category>
<category id="220" parentid="216" hentai="false" weight="500">
<name>Stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</category>
<category id="282" parentid="313" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>Ecchi</name>
<description>Ecchi, or etchi (エッチ), is a common Japanese word meaning "indecent", "lewd", "frisky" or "sexy"; its usage can be compared to the English word "naughty". Among western anime fans, the term is used when vague sexual content, such as skimpy clothing or nudity, is prominent. In Japanese, however, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, mild or otherwise.</description>
</category>
<category id="84" parentid="83" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Violence</name>
<description>Physical force against self or other, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.</description>
</category>
<category id="244" parentid="216" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Twisted</name>
<description>Twisted indicates more than one abrupt change in plot or story. This derivation from strict linear storytelling usually makes these anime hard to follow, and at times even very confusing when several parallel plots intertwine.</description>
</category>
<category id="252" parentid="313" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>Angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.&#13;
&#13;
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.&#13;
&#13;
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
</category>
<category id="15" parentid="313" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>Fantasy</name>
<description>Imaginative or fanciful work, especially one dealing with supernatural elements and themes.</description>
</category>
<category id="183" parentid="15" hentai="false" weight="500">
<name>Contemporary Fantasy</name>
<description>Magic and supernatural beings exist secretly in what is generally regarded as the real world. Such elements may have originated from another world. Stories where a modern-day character travels to an alternate fantasy world are not considered contemporary fantasy.</description>
</category>
<category id="369" parentid="282" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Breast Fondling</name>
<description>Part of the slapstick comedy in ecchi anime between female characters. E.g. a girl envious of another girl`s bust size may tease the latter via fondling. Usually playful and mischievous, not sexual.

Alas, now the tag can also imply "boob grabbing", where a male character will either accidentally or intentionally touch the breasts of a female. The former is a comedy element, as in "accidental infringement", the latter can be interpreted as a form of harassment.</description>
</category>
<category id="411" parentid="282" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Lingerie</name>
<description>The exposure of frilly (female) underwear plays a part in this anime. This could either be an ecchi element (think "paper clothes"), or may well be "job" clothing (e.g. a kinky super-heroine outfit).

This often also goes along with the shopping for lingerie, i.e. additional ecchi potential.</description>
</category>
<category id="285" parentid="153" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Violent Retribution for Accidental Infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).&#13;
&#13;
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</category>
<category id="230" parentid="198" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Love Polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
</category>
<category id="479" parentid="318" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Zettai Ryouiki</name>
<description>Japanese for "absolute area", and refers to an area of bare skin on the legs between a skirt and knee- or thigh-high stockings.</description>
</category>
<category id="482" parentid="175" hentai="false" weight="200">
<name>Magic Circles</name>
<description>A circle used to contain magical energy and/or to provide magical protection. It can be drawn (with chalk etc.) or it can just spontaneously appear as part of the spell/ritual.</description>
</category>
<category id="486" parentid="4" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Calling Your Attacks</name>
<description>If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.</description>
</category>
<category id="487" parentid="330" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Parental Abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.</description>
</category>
</categories>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10935</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>11226</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6682</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7739</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20557</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4948</identifier>
<identifier>rbzrgd</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4533</identifier>
<identifier>ftnfkh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dogakobo.com/works/11eyes.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://5pb.jp/games/11eyes/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://lass.jp/product/11eyes</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mmv.co.jp/special/11eyes/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11eyes:_Tsumi_to_Batsu_to_Aganai_no_Shōjo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11eyes_-罪と罰と贖いの少女-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1749</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334974</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11876</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>729</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>meta tags</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>lingerie</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1065" parentid="6149" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-01-13">
<name>heterochromatic eyes</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Heterochromia Iridis is a condition where one eye is a different color from the other, or one eye is more than one color.
Characters with different eye-colour may not necessarily have the medical condition itself, as the state of different-coloured eyes can be caused by various other reasons such as possession by spiritual entities, indication of special powers or artificial changes.
Can also be used to describe anime which portrays everyday scenery with unusual colours to draw attention or set a certain mood.</description>
<picurl>63229.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-14">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<count>1</count>
</tag>
<tag id="1719" parentid="6149" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-12-28">
<name>orphan</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The character (in common usage: only a child, or the young of an animal) has lost both parents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-25">
<name>tentacle</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-08">
<name>high school</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>a secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>magic</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2145" parentid="6149" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-11-21">
<name>chain</name>
<count>1</count>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-07-01">
<name>tsundere</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2544" parentid="6149" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-16">
<name>precognition</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The ability to see into the future. This can manifest as prophetic visions or could be more prosaic, such as the ability to see future events by means of some divinatory devices such as tarot cards or astrology, but such divination should be accurate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>content indicators</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>target audience</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>original work</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>What the anime is based on! Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>place</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>swordplay</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-06">
<name>super power</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>fantasy world</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>A fantasy world is a type of imaginary world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to magic or magical abilities and a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>large breasts</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Focus on larger than average breasts. Pretty common in anime. Usually involves adolescent girls or fully grown women.
Not to be confused with bigger and less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts], which means unnaturally large breasts</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-18">
<name>sex</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Known as intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting).</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-07-28">
<name>violence</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Physical force against self or other, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>love polygon</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-13">
<name>parallel universe</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Parallel universe/world or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we`ll use the term "Parallel Universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own universe (meaning a fantasy world can just as well have an alternative reality, doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 universe/reality/world is present in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>action</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-07">
<name>angst</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>comedy</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-10">
<name>romance</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-09-22">
<name>harem</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/l511 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-23">
<name>school life</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>female student</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>old animetags</name>
<count>1</count>
</tag>
<tag id="3175" parentid="2931" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-22">
<name>hand signs</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Characters form attacks through a succession of special hand signs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3552" parentid="2931" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-26">
<name>evil eye</name>
<count>1</count>
</tag>
<tag id="3908" parentid="6148" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2015-01-02">
<name>lap pillow</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>As a sign of closeness the usually male character is encouraged to rest his weary head on the female’s lap.</description>
<picurl>167007.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3926" parentid="6233" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-06-05">
<name>wardrobe limited to school uniform</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The main characters only wear school uniforms, even though other clothes would be more appropriate.
Example: Kagome in Inu Yasha, wears her uniform in Inu Yasha`s world, although she is shown to own other clothes at home.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-09-10">
<name>flashback</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously upheld from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content that hadn`t been previously shown; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4461" parentid="6233" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>seven deadly sins</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>The Seven Deadly Sins, also known as the Capital Vices or Cardinal Sins, are a classification of the most objectionable vices that have been "around" since early Christian times to educate and instruct followers concerning the (immoral) fallen man`s tendency to sin. These sins are: "Lust", "Gluttony", "Greed", "Sloth", "Wrath", "Envy", and "Pride".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>happy ending</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-01-10">
<name>protection complex</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.&#13;
&#13;
The magnitude of overprotection can vary.  It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe".  It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4709" parentid="6149" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-31">
<name>heavy smoking</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Someone in the story consumes more than one supply of their preferred method of inhaled substance by the end of the episode/series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5668" parentid="2931" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-04-09">
<name>just a flesh wound</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>character surviving a grievous bodily injury just fine.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<count>1</count>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
<count>1</count>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>tropes</name>
<count>1</count>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>ending</name>
<count>1</count>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" approval="100" spoiler="false" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
<count>1</count>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11046" type="main character in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="12">5.28</rating>
<name>Satsuki Kakeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satsuki Kakeru is the main protagonist in 11eyes. He and his sister were orphaned in their youth, and went to an orphanage where they first met Yuka. After his older sister committed suicide ten years prior to the main storyline, Kakeru felt that his life was empty. This was later filled by Yuka and his new friends he met in high school. He has heterochromia and wears an eyepatch over his right eye, known as the eye of Aeon, which holds what seems to be the power of precognition. It also shows him images of Velad, an ancient King of Drasuvania who also apparently possessed the eye. He is able to use his right eye in battle to predict and counter his opponent`s moves. In the VN, the real power of the eye of Aeon not only covers precognition, but also allows the bearer to assimilate all the memories and abilities of countless previous bearers. Ultimately, it also allows the bearer to realize the desired future out of all the possible futures there are. The price for those powers is that upon death, the bearer`s soul is absorbed into the eye as it`s being passed on to a new bearer. This explains why Kakeru dreams of Velad, who was the previous bearer of the eye. The Eye of Aeon is also a magic stone on its own and is not a fragment of Liselotte`s voidstone, nor can it increase her power; a complete opposite from the anime where it was the most important fragment. After this fact is revealed, the Black Knights is no longer after Kakeru`s life and he is given the option to walk away from the ongoing conflicts, although he decides to keep fighting with his friends.</description>
<picture>32928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11047" type="main character in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="25">2.35</rating>
<name>Minase Yuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minase Yuka is Kakeru`s childhood friend. She met him at the orphanage where they grew up, and was able to help Kakeru feel better after his sister`s suicide. She is in love with Kakeru. She is also in Kakeru`s class in school. In the later part of the story, she discovers that she also has a power that seems to negate others` powers. She and Kukuri name the power "Hand of Glory". However, it`s merely a misconception of her and other companions in the "Red Night". Later in the game, she was able to remember why the bloody event at Ayame orphanage, where she, Kakeru, and Kukuri used to live as orphans, happened. It turned out that because her power was awakened and she did not know how to control it at the time, it wreaked havoc in the orphanage. The orphans living there started to go insane and killed each other. She explained Kukuri and Kakeru weren`t affected due to Kukuri`s power nullifying hers. This event had such an impact on her that she sealed this portion of memories in her mind ever since and did not dare to go near the orphanage once she was adopted. Liselotte, while using her connection with the "fragments", tells Yuka that her power is "Phantasmagoria", a special technique/spell used by Liselotte herself. The power allows her to bring out others` worst memories or show people illusions of her own design. She explains that her power appears to nullify others because while being affected by Phantasmagoria, people unconsciously lose the will to maintain their power so it appears as though the power is nullified. While being conscious of her own power, she uses it to try to keep Kakeru to herself by using her power on the whole group and create an illusionary world. She later fades away and is absorbed by Liselotte because she uses up all her power creating the perfect world.</description>
<picture>32929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1671" picture="19766.jpg">Gotou Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11048" type="main character in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="26">8.73</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Misuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kusakabe Misuzu is a red-haired swordwoman. She is one year older than Yuka and Kakeru. She is an Onmyoji from the Kusakabe clan, a clan of Onmyoji that is famous for having Oni`s blood in the bloodline and the five demonic swords known as Kusakabe`s Five Treasures. Misuzu possesses all five swords, keeping them in her fingernails by using dimensional magic that she learned from forbidden scrolls that were created by one of her ancestors who learned and incorporated Western magic, Kusakabe Ryoichi. While she appears to be strong, Misuzu is the weakest mind of the group. She is traumatized when Misao reveals the truth about the "fragments". For a short few days when Misao gives the remainder of the group time to think over whether they decide to continue to be her and Avaritia`s opponents or to commit suicide themselves, Misuzu considers killing herself and is snapped back by Kakeru. Misuzu has feelings for Kakeru. In the final battle, she gives all she has to kill Misao by using Doujikiri Yasutsuna.</description>
<picture>32930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="34824.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11049" type="main character in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="12">6.33</rating>
<name>Tachibana Kukuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tachibana Kukuri is a strange girl in school who looks exactly like Kakeru`s dead sister. She is one year older than Yuka and Kakeru. She has the ability to material her soul into the form of an angel that appeared chained. She calls the angel "Abraxas". "Abraxas" attacks by sending out chains with sharp blades and has healing power. She is the adopted daughter of the famous novelist in the area whom she inherited her last name. She has no memories beyond five years ago, when she was 13, and seems to have lost her voice. She uses a sketchbook for communication. In one scene of 11eyes CrossOver, it is noted by Shuu indirectly that her power is very unique and incredibly difficult to reproduce by mages. The chains on Abraxas are actually representation of Kukuri`s lost memories. The chains are also seals of Abraxas power. In the final battle, due to Yuka`s power, her lost memories return to her and Abraxas is unchained. She reveals that she is in fact Satsuki Kukuri, Kakeru`s sister from an alternate reality. In her original reality, it was Kakeru who was killed in an experiment causing her to went berserk and destroy a whole facility. After that, she was transported to the current reality. She reveals that her parents aren`t dead but rather Kakeru, Yuka and she were abandoned due to their powers. She also reveals that Ayame orphanage is actually a place where children with powers are assembled for research and the founder of the place is one of Misuzu`s mother side ancestor. While unchained, Abraxas`s name is "Demiurge" and has godly powers. Her left eye can peak into the past while her right eye is similar to the precognition power of the Eye of Aeon. She also has the power of spontaneous generation of creating things from nothing.</description>
<picture>32931.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="329" picture="55683.jpg">Rikimaru Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11050" type="main character in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="15">7.54</rating>
<name>Hirohara Yukiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hirohara Yukiko is a lively girl who is later seen killing monsters mercilessly during the Red Night. She is a granddaughter of the Hirohara Zaibatsu, one of the richest houses in the 11eyes world. She came back to Japan from the nation Dransvania. Her primary power of regneration makes her almost immortal. She fights using two knives. Her positive personality is maintained by a self-hypnotic suggestion while she is wearing her glasses. When the glasses are removed, her eyes and personality turn into that of a killing machine. She is one year younger than Yuka and Kakeru. When Takahisa goes berserk due to Saiko`s death, she kills him as an act of mercy to free his mind from Liselotte`s influence. After killing Takahisa she realizes that she loved him. In the anime her fragment is ripped out by Superbia, killing her, while in the game she is absorbed by Liselotte.</description>
<picture>32932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2204" picture="23065.jpg">Ichimura Oma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11051" type="main character in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="11">6.10</rating>
<name>Tajima Takahisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tajima Takahisa is young man in school who is a pyrokineticist. He is in the same grade as Yuka and Kakeru, but is not from their class. His personality is brash and that of a loner and is easily identified with a grey mullet. He is now under the guardianship of Saeko. In his childhood, he was trying his best to survive after his parents abandoned him. Saeko was the one that took him in, but he has little to no respect for her in spite of that. Saeko first saw Tajima when she was hiding from the police. He was also the one who discovered the wall that prevents the characters from escaping the city and thus the Red Night. In the anime he lost control of himself and let the fire demon inside him take over. After destroying half the city he asked Yukiko to kill him before the fire demon completely took control of him. On 11eyes -Resona Forma- Takahisa has younger sister named Ema.</description>
<picture>32933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11052" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="14">6.76</rating>
<name>Momono Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momono Shiori is a "traditional magician" and is usually seen with a book. She seemed indifferent to the students who approached her in class at first but eventually warmed up to Kaori and Tadashi and grew to treasure them due to their friendly spirit. Her secret identity is that of an apostle of Index, the largest magical organization within the world of 11eyes and 3days. Her real name given by Index is "Ursula of the Bookshelf". She transferred to Kakeru`s school to monitor the place and report its situation to Index. Her assignment was due to the sudden disappearance of the last warden. She is extremely powerful and is a candidate for the next 14 saints, the highest officials within Index. However, her family line is cursed to be born without eyeballs. In her case, the curse is even worse and she couldn`t even move a finger. Her current body is a magical artifact that her brain and nervous system were transplanted into and which allows her to hold 5000 magical books within. The body operates by absorbing magical energy. In the anime she gave her fragment to Kakeru to send Liselotte to the space-time rift. She is a classmate of Yuka and Kakeru. One of the main heroines in 11eyes CrossOver.</description>
<picture>32934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1928" picture="151689.jpg">Hagiwara Emiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11053" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="9">4.88</rating>
<name>Natsuki Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuki Kaori is a good friend of Yuka and Kakeru, often seen hitting Tadashi due to his personality. She is also a classmate of Yuka and Kakeru. One of the main heroines in 11eyes CrossOver. Her involvement in 11eyes CrossOver is due to her being a target of the doppelganger.</description>
<picture>32935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="17988.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11054" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="8">5.02</rating>
<name>Teruya Tadashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teruya Tadashi is a good friend of Yuka and Kakeru, who is often hit by Kaori. His role in the story is that of the class clown and the perverted friend. He is a classmate of Yuka and Kakeru.</description>
<picture>32936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9884" picture="49741.jpg">Nemoto Kouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11055" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="13">8.57</rating>
<name>Akamine Saiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akamine Saiko is the doctor at the school. The current guardian of Takahisa. In her youth, she was the gang leader of an all girl gang called "Kurenai Tenyo".</description>
<picture>32937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12211" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-13">
<rating votes="5">4.44</rating>
<name>Avaritia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the black knights and determined to crush the "fragments". In actual, he is one of the 14 saints from Index, called "George of the Rainbow". He was sent out with his subordinates to eliminate Index top priority threat, Liselotte Wreckmeister. After a seemingly losing battle with Liselotte at Ayame`s Hill 70 years ago, he used his last resort, the forbidden technique, Contract of the Rainbow to split Liselotte`s soul and the piece of Emerald Tablet within her into seven fragments to weaken her. Liselotte with one of the fragments remains in her body was sealed within the crystal. The other fragments, due to the technique, was scattered across 6 parallel worlds. This explain why he calls the gang "fragments" because their bodies contain those "fragments" and those "fragments" are the sources of their powers. In his past mission, he sealed a dragon within his body with the same technique and release it in the final battle to crush the "fragments" and Liselotte with the price of losing himself. It took a lot out of him to maintain seal of the dragon within his body and at the same time Liselotte`s seal.</description>
<picture>40202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12213" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="4">4.31</rating>
<name>Satsuki Kukuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kakeru`s dead sister. She killed herself seven years ago right in front of Kakeru.</description>
<picture>149592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="329" picture="55683.jpg">Rikimaru Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12541" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="8">6.29</rating>
<name>Superbia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most powerful Black Knight after Avaritia. She fights using two Japanese swords that are similar to Misuzu`s. She is in fact the only Black Knight who has no association with Index. Rather, she is actually Kusakabe Misao, the Kusakabe onmyoji that Misuzu admires. She reveals that her two swords were part of Kusakabe`s treasures. The swords she has, Onikiri and Kumokiri, in additions to Misuzu`s, were once referred as Kusakabe`s Seven Swords. After she took the two swords and leave her clan, the swords that Misuzu has then become Kusakabe`s Five Treasures. In the game, she looks down on all the "fragments" and Kakeru except Shiori because only Shiori is strong enough to fight her. She is also the only member of the Black Knight who is actually alive or living without burden. The four subordinate of George are actually death and their souls is bounded by her with Larva(the Red Night`s creatures) as their bodies. She also sealed their memories they have while they are alive. She also contribute part of her power help keeping the dragon sealed within George. It is hinted that she helps George and his group because she admires and loves him.
She is named after one of the 7 Cardinal Sins, pride (superbia in latin).</description>
<picture>39822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="650" picture="18177.jpg">Hyousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12542" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="11">6.18</rating>
<name>Lisette Weltall</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lisette Weltall is the girl in the crystal who ties deeply with the world of the "Red Night" itself. While she is naturally good at heart, she has a split personality known as Liselotte Wreckmeister. It is Liselotte who is the master of the "Red Night".</description>
<picture>39301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1664" picture="19755.jpg">Niina Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12543" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="6">3.51</rating>
<name>Ira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second Black Knight to be slain. Killed by Kakeru, a slimly muscular male with predatory slanted red eyes and is armed with syths embedded on his fore arms. He is specialised in Chinese martial art. He is actually an apostle of Index and at the same time a subordinate of George of the Rainbow. His index`s name is "Sebastian of the Holy Bone".</description>
<picture>39828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3831" picture="49743.jpg">Fujiwara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12544" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="6">3.68</rating>
<name>Invidia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the only female Black Knight beside Superbia and is the only member with wings that can fly. She use a sword that resemble a spine that specialize for long range attack. The fourth knight to be killed. She plans to explode herself and take down everyone in Kakeru`s gang with her. Her attempt fails due to Yuka`s awaken power and Yukiko killed her by stabbing on her forehead. She is also a subordinate of George of the Rainbow and her Index`s name is "Elayce of the Dragon Skeleton". In the game, it is revealed that she loves Sebastian.</description>
<picture>39827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="329" picture="55683.jpg">Rikimaru Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12545" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="6">1.96</rating>
<name>Acedia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The "mage" of the group, as he is after the bearer of the eye of Aeon. It uses scrolls as his weapon. He is quickly killed by Kukuri, however one part of it`s head "scholastica" manage to fled causing it to survive. However it is killed by Shiori afterwards. In the game, his two parted head is cut down by Misuzu using Doujikiri and Scholastica dies at this time instead and Acedia is killed by Shiori afterwards. Scholastica is actually Acedia`s sister and they share a body. His Index`s name is "Benedict of the Bookshelf". It is revealed by Shiori that Benedict and George are people in her family line. Shiori refers to him as her prototype when she kills him.
It is named after one of the 7 Cardinal Sins, discouragement (acedia in latin), today referred to as sloth.
Its real identity is the historical figure of Saint Benedict of Nursia.</description>
<picture>39824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10744" picture="38665.jpg">Naruke Yoshiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12546" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="6">2.48</rating>
<name>Gula</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the Black Knights, whose figure is a giant fat male with a club as it`s weapon. It is also the first one to die. Was killed by Misuzu. His role in the story and within the Black Knight group is most minor. His Index`s name is "Samson of the Holy Club".</description>
<picture>39826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5406" picture="29630.jpg">Tanzawa Teruyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12715" type="appears in" update="2009-11-26">
<rating votes="5">6.55</rating>
<name>Verard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>King of Drasvenia, a kingdom that existed in Eastern Europe during the Middle Ages, and where Yukiko came from. His right eye is golden, similar to that of Kakeru.</description>
<picture>39302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="66" picture="16671.jpg">Bifu Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13269" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="6">1.79</rating>
<name>Scholastica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second head part of Acedia. It was killed by Shiori.
Scholastica is actually Acedia`s sister and they share a body.
Its real identity is the historical figure of Scholastica, a Catholic saint and the twin sister of St. Benedict of Nursia, who is the identity of Acedia.</description>
<picture>39303.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13270" type="appears in" update="2009-11-26">
<rating votes="7">6.07</rating>
<name>Liselotte Werkmeister</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The girl in the crystal who ties deeply with the world of the "Red Night" itself. While she is naturally good at heart, she has a split personality known as Liselotte Wreckmeister. It is Liselotte who is the master of the "Red Night".</description>
<picture>39301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1664" picture="19755.jpg">Niina Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13598" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="11">7.41</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Misao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most powerful onmyoji of the Kusakabe clan. She lived 70 years ago and got hold of all the Kusakabe`s Seven Treasures. She is admired by Misuzu.
It is later revealed that the black knight Superbia is in fact her.</description>
<picture>39823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="650" picture="18177.jpg">Hyousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13600" type="appears in" update="2009-12-06">
<rating votes="2">4.68</rating>
<name>Kuro Kishi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The black knights are saints from Index sent out to eliminate Liselotte Wreckmeister.
After a seemingly losing battle with Liselotte at Ayame`s Hill 70 years ago, Avaritia, "George of the Rainbow", used his last resort, the forbidden technique, Contract of the Rainbow to split Liselotte`s soul and the piece of Emerald Tablet within her into seven fragments to weaken her. Liselotte with one of the fragments remains in her body was sealed within the crystal. The other fragments, due to the technique, were scattered across 6 parallel worlds.
Kakeru and the others are those fragments and are now the main threat for the Black Knights.</description>
<picture>39829.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13709" type="appears in" update="2009-12-28">
<name>Kyomu no Kakera</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>"Fragments" originating from the Emerald Tablet. It is said that using the Emerald Tablet it becomes possible to attain god`s wisdom and infinite magical power.
Because of the great power within, the Tablet was broken in the past into 12 fragments and scattered throughout the worlds thus becoming lost forever.
Liselotte Wreckmeister tried to collect all of the fragments but even for her it was only possible to collect five of them within the span of 700 years.
After her defeat by the hands of George of the Rainbow (Avaritia) and the other saints, the piece she collected was broken into seven fragments, the Fragments of Nothingness, five of which are found in Kakeru`s friends, with Kakeru himself holding the Eye of Aion, and the remaining two being embedded in Shiori and Liselotte/Lisette herself.
The Black Knights, who are in reality saints of Index, target the group to eliminate the threat of the fragments being collected once again.</description>
</character>
<character id="13710" type="appears in" update="2009-12-25">
<rating votes="3">1.66</rating>
<name>Kinsho Mokuroku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Index Librorum Prohibitorum ("List of Prohibited Books") was a list of publications prohibited by the Roman Catholic Church and the name of a secret organisation under the Vatican to monitor and if necessary stop the publication and distribution of works that were deemed as heretical and dangerous to the Church. Its members are adept in combat techniques and posses magical powers.
Although officially abolished on 14 June 1966 by Pope Paul VI, the Index is still being kept, although its activities are being kept to a minimum because of possible political implications.
----
Picture: Title page of Index Librorum Prohibitorum (Venice 1564).</description>
<picture>40594.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13716" type="appears in" update="2009-12-17">
<rating votes="7">3.19</rating>
<name>Abraxas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40282.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13717" type="appears in" update="2009-12-17">
<rating votes="5">2.11</rating>
<name>Georgius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The world`s mightiest dragon, possessing the power to destroy all evil.</description>
<picture>40284.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31173" type="appears in" update="2011-04-14">
<rating votes="5">4.79</rating>
<name>Satsuki Kakeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2980" picture="147242.jpg">Kanada Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31174" type="appears in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="5">3.98</rating>
<name>Tajima Takahisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="25072.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="108383" update="2009-09-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い夜 Piros éjszaka</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109180" update="2009-10-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水晶の少女 egy lány -ban kristály</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl in the Crystal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suishou no Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109234" update="2010-04-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109271" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤独な誇り egyedülálló büszkeség</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lonely Pride</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodoku na Hokori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109272" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仮面の微笑 a doboz mögött maszk</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Smiling Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamen no Bishou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109273" update="2009-10-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友と明日のために barátoknak, holnapra</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Friends and Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo to Ashita no Tame ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111220" update="2009-11-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心乱れて szíbtép fájdalom</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disturbed Minds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro Midarete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111353" update="2009-11-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歪んだ覚醒 kanyargós ébredés</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Twisted Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuganda Kakusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111407" update="2009-11-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逢魔が時 félhomály öv</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Witching Hour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ouma ga Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111719" update="2009-11-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壊れた絆 törött kötés</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Broken Bonds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kowareta Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111725" update="2009-11-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔女覚醒 bukott angyal</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Witch Awakens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majo Kakusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111726" update="2009-11-28">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">滅亡という選択 válogatott-hoz kialvás</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Option of Destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Metsubou to Iu Sentaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111727" update="2009-11-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇夜の暁 a sötét hajnal</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dawn of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anya no Yoake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116466" update="2010-04-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116962" update="2010-07-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">1.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桃色幻夢譚 ～rö zsaszí n é jszaka</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pink Dream Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Momoiro Genmutan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121389" update="2012-06-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121390" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121391" update="2012-06-23">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133104" update="2011-09-21">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ストレンジ・サービス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Strange Service</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133105" update="2012-06-23">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">友と明日のために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo to Asu no Tame ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133106" update="2011-09-21">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と誠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Makoto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133107" update="2012-06-23">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">死に至る病</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi ni Itaru Yamai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133108" update="2011-09-21">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">壊れた絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kowareta Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133109" update="2012-06-23">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">草壁の血</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kusakabe no Chi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133110" update="2011-09-21">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤンデレのゆかちゃんに死ぬほど愛されて眠れない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yandere no Yuka-chan ni Shinu hodo Aisarete Nemurenai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133111" update="2011-09-21">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">変わらぬ未来, 変わる過去</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaranu Mirai, Kawaru Kako</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133112" update="2011-09-21">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵を知り己を知れば百戦危うからず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki o Shiri Onore o Shireba Hyakusen Ayaukarazu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133113" update="2011-09-21">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒考現学部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro Kougengakubu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133114" update="2012-06-23">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">死に様の美学</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi ni Zama no Bigaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133115" update="2012-06-23">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">主人公属性</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shujinkou Zokusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133116" update="2011-09-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒騎士で学ぶ萌えアピール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro Kishi de Manabu Moe Appeal</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
